<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Shahrear Iqbal</title>
    <link>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Shahrear Iqbal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Shahrear Iqbal</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous/Connected Vehicle Security</title>
      <link>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/car/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/car/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity is one of the biggest threats in autonomous cars as vehicle connectivity is a new paradigm and the technology continues to evolve rapidly. One of the central challenges in vehicle cybersecurity is to secure the communication between various electronic components in a car (known as electronic control units, or ECUs) which are connected via an internal network. If hackers manage to gain access to a vulnerable, peripheral ECU (e.g., the Bluetooth or infotainment system), they may be able to take control of other safety-critical ECUs like brakes or the engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating System Security</title>
      <link>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/sam/</guid>
      <description>Smartphones have become an integral part of our daily lives that offer a multitude of features in a small form factor. Users store sensitive personal information on their phones and perform financial transactions. Moreover, people use their personal phones to access corporate/government resources and vice versa. We perform tasks on smartphones that require multiple security models to execute the tasks securely. However, most smartphone operating systems need to focus on the usability which compromises security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Devices from Click-Fraud</title>
      <link>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cs.queensu.ca/~iqbal/project/cf/</guid>
      <description>Pay-Per-Click (PPC) ad networks charge advertisers for every click on their ads. Click-fraud happens when a user or an automated software clicks on an ad with a malicious intent and advertisers need to pay for those valueless clicks. Click-fraud has been proved to be a serious problem for the online advertisement industry. Although it has attracted much attention from the security community, the direct victims of click-fraud, the advertisers, still lack confidence in the click-fraud detection techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>